http://www.circadian.com/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
CIRCADIAN.COM PRIVACY POLICY
Circadian.com, and its parent, Circadian Information Limited Partnership, a member of the international network of CIRCADIAN™ companies, are both committed to protecting your privacy and the security of your personal identifying information.  This Privacy Policy details how we use your personal identifying information. This Privacy Policy may be modified at any time without notice to you. Please review this document each time you visit us or use any of our tools or services.
We will never reveal your personal information to any third party or entity--accept under the following circumstances.
If a governmental agency, or an attorney, subpoenas your private information, or makes a formal request for discovery pursuant to any legal action, or pending legal action.
If our attorney requests such information relevant to a current or pending legal matter in which you are a potential or actual party or otherwise contributed in some way to the causation of the legal matter.
CookiesPlease note that we employ the use of cookies.  Currently we employ cookies when users create user accounts, but we may further employ cookies to assist the functionality of other tools, services and functions in the future.
Cookies are small programs that enhance your use of the Internet, in general, and specifically we use cookies to enhance your usage of our functions.
As you employ our functions, your user name, password and email address is recorded in our database. A session cookies is written to your browser for the purpose of maintaining an authenticated session with you, the user.
The information gathered is not shared with third parties. You may turn off your cookies by adjusting the appropriate setting on your browser.
Please consult the HELP menu of your browser to learn how to turn your cookies off. Cookies do not reveal personal information and if you turn off your cookies you may find your enjoyment of the Internet, and our site, to be reduced or impaired.
General InformationIn order to seek out and repair functionality issues with our servers and related programming, we may use your email and IP addresses for evaluation and diagnostic purposes.
We may also use your email and IP addresses to automatically recognize you should you contact us or use our tools and services. Groups of email and IP addresses are also gathered so that we may have broad demographic information.
You may be required to complete online registration forms that provide us with contact information (such as your name and street address), your email address, and your phone numbers.
We may, from time to time, send you emails regarding our service so that we can directly communicate with you regarding issues we determine to be relevant. We may also provide you with promotional information about our tools and services, as well as tools and services offered by our partners. An opt-out procedure is provided with each mailing regarding general offers or information. You must accept emails from us that deal with specific issues regarding your account or membership. This is because we may need to contact you if there is a change in the service that we are providing you or if we need to respond to an inquiry that you have sent us regarding a customer service issue or other important concern.
Naturally, should you purchase a product or service through Circadian.com, we will require sufficient information from you so that we can complete the transaction. Such information could include a credit card number and related account and billing data, invoice related information, and other data required for processing the order. We will also update such data should you grant us permission to bill you or your credit card for recurring charges, such as monthly or other types of periodic payments. All information of this nature is maintained by us in a secure database and transmitted across the Internet from you to us using secured transmission encryption.
Please contact us if you should have any questions, comments or concerns about this privacy policy.
Home  |  Privacy Policy  |  Terms of Use  |  Sitemap  |  Contact Us
Sign Up to Receive CIRCADIAN News.Optional email address
Sign Up
Circadian Headquarters 2 Main Street, Suite 310 Stoneham, MA, 02180, USA
Contact InformationEmail: info@circadian.comLocal: 1.781.439.6300
©2020 Circadian ZircLight, Inc.All rights reserved.
Home24/7 Industries Aviation CAS-5 Fatigue Risk ModelCrew Planning with our Partners at AD OPTFACTS - Aviation Fatigue Incident AnalysisFRMS Training, AuditsFRMS Consulting & ResearchEnergy Oil & GasPipelines Controller Workload Assessment ProgramFatigue Training Options for PipelinesNuclear PowerElectric UtilitiesDiscrete Manufacturing AutomotiveElectronicsHi Tech & SemiconductorPharma & BiotechMining & Metals MiningPrimary MetalsFoundriesNursing and Health CareOther Transportation Marine & Ports Marine & Port Pilots FRMSPublic TransitRailroadsTruckingLogistics & WarehousingProcess Manufacturing Chemicals & PlasticsPaper & PulpFoodPersonal CareServices Media & CommunicationsPolice, Fire, EMSPrintingChallenges Cost Reduction AbsenteeismEmployee TurnoverHealthcareOvertimeStaffing LevelsSafety and Legal LiabilityErrors & Accidents Fatigued EmployeesNight Shift ErrorsImpaired EmployeesAccident LitigationScheduling Shifts Choosing Shift SchedulesAdjusting to ShiftworkEducating ManagersExpanding to 7 DayLight Exposure at NightEfficient 24/7 Utilization Corporate Shiftwork StrategyExpanding to 7 Day OperationsStaffing LevelsEmployee Relations TrainingUnion/Labor IssuesWork and Family Life BalanceRegulatory Burdens Hours of ServiceFMLAWork Hours LitigationSolutions Shift Scheduling Shift Schedule OptimizationExpanding to 7 Day OperationsProportional StaffingShiftwork Opportunity AssessmentBest Practices BenchmarkingScientific Literature Review24/7 Workplace Evaluation and DesignFatigue Risk Management Systems (FRMS) How to Design a Fatigue Risk Management System (FRMS)Gap Analysis of Your FRMSCreating an Effective FRMS: The CIRCADIAN Tools You Need Sleep Disorder ScreeningCIRCADIAN's FRMS ExpertiseEducation & Training On-Site Workshop Shiftwork Scheduling and Staffing Best PracticesSuccessfully Expanding from 5- to 7-Day OperationsDeveloping and Implementing an Effective Fatigue Risk Management SystemManagement SeminarsManaging a Shiftwork LifestyleTrain the TrainerFatigue Training OnlineCIRCADIAN SeminarsCorporate Sleep ProgramsCircadian Light TechnologyRisk & Cost Assessment Shiftwork Opportunity AssessmentStaffing Level AnalysisFatigue Risk AssessmentTechnology AssessmentAccident/Incident AnalysisShiftworker Health and Adaptation AssessmentHuman Fatigue Expert Witness Testimony Fatigue-Related Accident LitigationRegulatory ChallengesWork Hours LitigationContact Circadian Expert ServicesPublications & Reports Management ReportsTraining MaterialsEmployee PublicationsWhite PapersEmergency Services SchedulingSoftware Fatigue Risk Management Software AircrewShiftworkerAccident-Incident Analysis with FACTSFatigue Training OnlineAircrewDriverShiftworkerSupervisorPublications Management ReportsTraining MaterialsEmployee PublicationsWhite PapersShifting Work PerspectivesManaging 24-Hour OperationsCIRCADIAN StoreAbout Us About CIRCADIANHistoryLeadershipPartnersResearch & TechnologyNewsCareer OpportunitiesContact
